# PROFILE

# David Tjomsland

I am a passionate and patient individual that strives to better myself through positivity, self-motivation, and team building. I am a team player that communicates openly and with encouragements. My past experience in the service industry and as a teacher has taught me how to always keep a level head and problem solve no matter the circumstances. I think on my feet and enjoy working outside of the box for any challenges that come my way.

# **CONTACT**



04 5636 2857

11 Conroy Street Maylands WA 6051

dtjomslandjr@gmail.com

## **SKILLS**



#### PROFESSIONAL

Basic Front-end Development •
Microsoft • Excel • Microsoft Word •
Adept Teacher • Works Well Under
Pressure

### PERSONAL

Self Motivated • Creative Thinker • Continually Positive • Team Player • Eloquent • Versatile • Outgoing • Friendly • Flexible • Organized • Dedicated Leadership



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### PHYSICS/SPECIAL EDUCATION TEACHER

February 2015 - 2019

#### MANTECA UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT - MANTECA, CA

Create and execute lesson plans in a way that is engaging for students • Nurture a positive environment that facilitates learning for all • Ensure a sustainable relationship with parents, pupils, school personnel and members of the public by communicating in a confidential, polite and refined manner • Teach students skills to live and thrive • Adapt to individual needs of students so none are left behind • Outline and enforce classroom expectations daily • Reacting quickly to ensure behaviors do not escalate

#### **RELIEF TEACHER**

August 2014 - January 2015

#### MANTECA UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT - MANTECA, CA

Provide classwork and homework assignments • Ensure effective discipline and class control. • Adapt to varying demographics daily • Create impromptu lesson plans when instructions are absent • Adhere to all procedures, guidelines, and policies followed by regular teachers • Quickly become familiar with the lesson plan and subject in order to assist students with their assignment

#### ASSISTED LIVING

February - August 2013

#### CENTRAL VALLEY TRAINING CENTER - STOCKTON. CA

Support client through daily activities • Provide proper medication on schedule • Guarantee safety of client • Assist in creation a safe home environment • Assess living conditions, mental well-being, and overall care • Create detailed logs of witnessed behaviors



0

# **EDUCATION**

#### WEB DEVELOPMENT

2020 - Present
North Metro TAFE

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE**

2010 - 2012

B.A. History and Native American Studies
University of California, Santa Barbara

#### ASSOCIATE'S DEGREE

2008 - 2010

A.A. Social and Behavioral Science
San Joaquin Delta College